(Sheldon:)...and I was forced to issue
an undeserved apology...
...because I refused to urinate in
a stainless-steel bowl in front of criminals.
(Howard:)Plus, you didn't get to meet Stan Lee.
(Leonard:)Okay, that's enough, Howard.
The poor guy's had a tough time.
(Leonard:)He had to spend the entire afternoon
in jail wearing that suit.
(Howard:)It would be cruel to mention that,
after he finished signing autographs...
(Howard:)...Stan Lee took Stuart and us out
for gelato.
(Sheldon:)You had gelato with Stan Lee?
(Howard:)He said we could call him Stan.
(Leonard:)Except for Raj.
(Sheldon:)Well, I hope you're satisfied, Penny.
(Sheldon:)You are responsible for all the evil
that has befallen me today.
(Penny:)-I realize--
SHELDON: Not finished.
(Sheldon:)It is because of you
that I now have a criminal record.
(Sheldon:)And it is because of you that I missed out
on having gelato with Stan Lee.